http://www.jerrysartarama.com/privacy-info

Login
Forgot Password ?
Product Icon Details
Search:
0
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Go To Cart/Shop By Item#: Click Here >
Cart
Shop All
Shop All Categories Coupon Eligible Supplies Buy Bulk - Save More Clearance Art Supplies Mixed Media Supplies Art Painting Party Supplies Portfolios & Presentation Cases Printmaking Supplies Eco-Friendly Supplies Printmaking Supplies Art Education Supplies See All Categories>
Shop By Alphanumeric: #, A, B, C..Professional PaintsProfessional BrushesProfessional CanvasCustom Framing Custom Stretched CanvasGift Cards/eGift Cards
"I have been a loyal customer..it has been a 15 year relationship now. Thank you Jerry's!"
Paints & Mediums
Acrylic Paints & Mediums Soho Artist Acylic Paints Charvin Extra Fine Artist Acrylics LUKAS Cryl AcrylicsGOLDEN Acrylics & Mediums Turner Acryl GouacheLiquitex Acrylics & Mediums Pouring Paints & Mediums Creative Inspirations AcrylicsSee Full List >
Water-Mixable Oil PaintsLUKAS Berlin Water-Mixable OilsGrumbacher Max OilsDANIEL SMITH Water Soluble OilsCobra Water-Mixable OilsMarie's Water Soluble Oil Colors See Full List >
Oil Color Paints & Mediums LUKAS 1862 Oil Colors & MediumsCharvin Artist Oil Colors & MediumsGamblin Artists' Oil ColorsWinsor & Newton Artist Oil ColorsSoho Artist OilsGrumbacher Pre-Tested Oils Rembrandt OilsOld Holland Classic Oils See Full List > Sprays, Varnishes & Fixatives Palettes Artist Aprons & Smocks Painting Supplies Gessos & Priming Materials Encaustics Glass Paints
Watercolor Paints & MediumsTurner Professional Watercolors Lukas Aquarell 1862 Watercolors Golden QOR Watercolors Winsor & Newton Professional Water Colours Daniel Smith Extra Fine Watercolors Sennelier Artist Watercolors & Sets Masking Tapes & Fluids See Full List > Pouring Paints & Mediums Printmaking Supplies Watercolor Gouache Egg Tempera & Casein Color Mixing Guides Dry Pigments & Binder Mediums
Featured Special
Solvent Free Oil Paints
Gamblin Gamsol
"Jerry's makes my love for painting possible. Affordable outstanding discounts & better paints!"
Canvas & Surfaces
Canvas, Panels & Rolls Panels HeadquartersStretched CanvasCanvas RollsCanvas Pads Panels Canvas Boards Canvas Mounted To Panels AlumaComp Aluminum Panels Gessoed AlumaComp PanelsCustom Stretched Canvas Multi-Media Liquid Art Panels Canvas w/ Aluminum Frames See Full List >
Professional Cotton Canvas Canvas Super Value 5 Packs Practica Stretched Canvas Senso Linen All Media Panels Unprimed Cotton Duck RollsArtFix Belgian Linen Canvas Rolls Claessens Linen Canvas RollsFredrix Artist CanvasesCenturion Deluxe Oil Primed Linen Rolls Gesso And Primers Canvas Tools & Accessories Canvas Carriers Canvas Bridge Canvas Print Racks
Stretcher Strips & Cross BracesGallery Pro Stretchers & Cross BracesProfile Extra Deep Stretcher Strips & Cross Braces Museo Aluminum Stretcher Bars Heavy Duty White Pine Stretcher Bars BEST Aluminum Stretcher Bars & Cross BracesSee Full List >
Featured Special
Custom Canvas Department
Heavy Duty Stretcher Bars
"My go-to place to buy quality art supplies. Great service. I save a lot of money"
Brushes & Tools
Artist Brushes Oil & Acrylic Brushes Watercolor Brushes Synthetic Oil & Acrylic Brushes Synthetic Watercolor Brushes Sword Liners & Striper Brushes Detail Brushes Classroom Brush Packs Specialty Brushes Color Shapers See Full List >
Professional Brushes Oil & Acrylic Brushes Creative Mark Oil & Acrylic Brushes Hamburg Premier Professional Brushes Imperial Professional Bristle Brushes Mimik Hog Synthetic Brushes Mimik Kolinsky Synthetic Sable Black Swan Red Sable Brushes Pro Stroke Powercryl Ultimate Acrylic Brushes Silver Brush Oil & Acrylic Brushes Simmons Oil & Acrylic Brushes Raphael Oil & Acrylic Brushes Princeton Oil & Acrylic Brushes DuraHandle Resin Handle Brushes See Full List >
Palette Knives
FX Palette Knives Plastic Palette Knives Painters Edge Steel Palette Knives
Catalyst Blades
See Full List > Brush Storage Brush Easels & Travel Cases Brush & Hand Cleaners Brush Washers Aquatote Travel Water Bags Brush Crate
Featured Special
Brush Crate Artist Brush Holder
"A large selection of unusual items seldom available from other companies. I'm hooked on Jerry's!"
Easels & Furniture
EaselsDisplay Easels Studio EaselsTable Top Easels H-Frame EaselsA-Frame Easels French Style Easels Wall Easels Convertible Easels Metal Easels Large Electric Easel Kids Easels See Full List >
Studio Furniture Studio Organizers Print & Drying Racks Chairs & Stools Flat FilesAir PurifiersPaint & Sketch BoxesDrawing Tables & SetsTaborets Lighting See Full List >
Projectors & LightboxesAcurit Thin Line Pro LED Light BoxesArtograph Projectors & LightboxesKopyKake Projectors
Travel & Outdoor Easels Lightweight & Field Easels Field Studio Supplies Pochade Boxes Umbrellas & Shade
Picture & Artwork Lights Easel AccessoriesHand Trucks & TrolleysCanvas & Frame Carts
Featured Special
Best Selling Table Easel
All Media Lightweight Easel
"As a professional artist I use a lot of supplies and I've been shopping at Jerry's since 1996!"
Framing, Mats/Boards
Frames Ready Made Frames Millbrook Ready Made Collection Plein Air Frames
Museum Plein Air Frames Ambiance Gallery Wood Frames Canvas Floater Frames Frame Glass & Styrenes Ambiance Gallery Aluminum Frames Custom Framing Certificate Frames Kids Art Frames See Full List > Picture Framing Lights Films & Acetate Tapes & Adhesives Frame Glass & Styrenes Frame Shipping Supplies
Foam & Backing Boards Jerry's Acid Free Pro Foam Boards View Point Backing Boards Acid Free Foam Core Boards Foamwerks Cutting Tools See Full List > Framing Hardware & EquipmentCanvas Offset Clips Hanging Equipment Logan Frame Backing Kit Picture Hanging Wire Canvas Hanging Supplies See Full List >
Mat Board, Pre-Cut Mats, Supplies Pyramid Pre Cut Mat Packs Crescent Pre Cut 10 PacksCrescent RagMat Museum Boards Viewpoint Acid Free Foam Backing Pre Cut Mat Packs W/Krystal Seal Bags See Full List > Mat & Paper Cutters Logan Mat Cutters X-Acto Paper Cutters Self Healing Mats
Featured Special
Custom Frame Department
Extra-Deep Black Gallery Frames
"I am a constant customer and "recommender". I order all of my gallery supplies & lots of frames!"
Drawing Supplies
Colored Pencils SoHo Colored Pencils & Sets Cezanne Professional Colored PencilsFaber-Castell Polychromos Pencils Prismacolor Colored PencilsCaran d'Ache Colored Pencils Bruynzeel Colored Pencil Sets Raffiné Colored Pencil Sets See Full List >
Art Markers & Pens Concept Dual Tip MarkersCOPIC Markers Tombow Brush Pens, Markers & Marker Sets Acurit Technical PensFaber-Castell Pitt Artist Pens High Flow Acrylic MarkersMicron PensPrismacolor MarkersSee Full List >
Charcoal Creative Mark Willow Charcoal Cretacolor Charcoal Derwent Charcoal Cretacolor Charcoal Faber-Castell Pitt Charcoal Conté À Paris See Full List >
Pencils, Leads & Powders Jerry's Jumbo Jet Charcoal Pencils Faber-Castell Pencils & Graphite Caran D'Ache Neocolor II CrayonsCretacolor Pencils, LeadsSakura Mechanical PencilsStaedtler Drawing PencilsPastel Pencils Watercolor Pencils & Sticks See Full List >
Perspective ToolsManikinsProportional Divider See Full List >
PastelsOil PastelsSemi-Hard PastelsSoft PastelsPastel Accessories
Calligraphy & LetteringInksWatercolor Pencils & Sticks Drafting SuppliesDrawing Tools
Erasers Pencil Sharpeners Sprays & Fixatives Pencil Cases
Featured Special
"I draw, paint, sculpt & carve. I know that I can save money on the best materials at Jerry's"
Paper & Pads
Drawing, Multimedia Paper & BoardsLiquid Art Multi-Media PanelsStrathmore Drawing PadsStrathmore Vision Mixed MediaReflexions Drawing & Sketch JournalsCrescent Illustration BoardsStonehenge Multi Media PadsSee Full List > Mixed Media Papers & Pads Stonehenge Aqua Watercolor PapersYupo Multimedia PaperStrathmore Paper PadsFabriano Drawing PapersJerry's Colossal Deluxe SketchpadsStonehenge Multi Media PadsSee Full List > Greeting Cards & Postcards Strathmore Greeting CardsFabriano Medioevalis Greeting CardsSee Full List >
Acrylic & Oil Paper & Boards Arches Oil Paper Strathmore Canvas PadsAmpersand Gessobord PanelsSee Full List > Printmaking Paper Strathmore Printmaking Paper Speedball Arnhem 1618 Paper Stonehenge Paper & PadsArches Cover PaperRives BFK PaperCanson Edition PaperSee Full List > Pastel Paper & BoardsAmpersand
PastelbordArt Spectrum ColourfixPremier Sanded Pastel PaperRicheson Unison Pastel SurfacesSennelier Pastel Papers & PadsCanson Mi TeintesSee Full List >
Watercolor Paper & SurfacesFabriano Artistico Watercolor Paper Arches Watercolor Paper Winsor & Newton Professional Watercolor Blocks Stonehenge Aqua Watercolor PapersYupo Multimedia PaperCanson Heritage Watercolor PaperStrathmore 300 Series Pads Fluid 100 Watercolor Paper Ampersand Museum Series AquabordSee Full List > Sketchbooks
Inkjet and Digital Papers Awagami Rice Paper Artist Trading CardsDecorative PapersMarker PaperTransfer PaperVellum
Featured Special
SoHo Open Bound Sketch Pads
"Jerry's carries all the paper I need for my watercolor. I get what I need at the lowest prices"
Artist Resources
FREE Video Art Lessons Art Lessons By Medium Art Lessons By Subject Art Lessons By Skill Art Education Lessons BooksAdult Coloring Books & SuppliesPepin Adult Coloring BooksNorth Light Educational & Adult Coloring Books Artists Handbook Of Materials & Techniques See Full List >
DVD LessonsAcrylic Painitng LessonsOil Painting LessonsMixed Media LessonsSketching & DrawingDVDsWatercolor Painting Lessons Art Programs & Kits Virtual Art Classes for Kids
Paint Along Wilson Bickford
Home Art School Grades K-5
Reel Art AcademySTART Art Program See Full List >
Jerry's LIVE - LIVE Art Events
Jerry's Artist BlogTeacher/Student Supply Lists Online Art Contests Best Sellers My Story - Enter Yours Artist Spotlight
What's Trending
Have Fun, Create Art
Find/Create Supply Lists
"I'm grateful for the high-quality resources that Jerry's provides"
ALL NEW
ON SALE
<X Shop
Doorbuster Deals
HOLIDAY SALE
Gift Guide
Gift Sets
eGift & Gift Cards
SHOP BY ALPHABET
Shop By Letter: A, B, C....
>
ARTIST RESOURCES & SPECIALS
Jerry's LIVE - LIVE Art Instruction
Jerry's Artists Artwork
Art Educators Supply Lists
Bulk Art Supplies
Jerry's Artist Blog
FREE Video Art Lessons
Art Resources/Education
>
Hello, Sign In
Privacy Policy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for jerrysartarama.com (JERRY'S ARTARAMA). This web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, so it has agreed to disclose its information practices.
If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should contact Customer Service at 1-800-U-ARTIST by phone.
Information Collection and Use
JERRY'S ARTARAMA is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. JERRY'S ARTARAMA collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.
Order
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user
Security
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the
bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage.
If you have any questions about our security policy, you can send an email to [email protected].
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Registered Trademarks
Some of the content seen on the site are registered trademarks of other companies and or vendors who supply us with products and payment options
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.jerrysartarama.com 6104 Maddry Oaks Ct Raleigh, North Carlolina 27616 USA [email protected] 1-800-827-8478
Where Artists Save on Art Supplies
Free & Fast Shipping @$45+#isaveatjerrys >
Personalized & Expert Service
Call Us 800-827-8478
#
A
B
C
Email Exclusive Club
Subscribe and receive coupon specials, great promos & VIP offers!
FREE Gift + BONUS COUPON & Free Shipping
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
eGift Cards & Gift Cards
Send One Now
Check Your Balance
Connect With Us
Need Help?
At Your Service
Contact Us
Shipping Info
Order Status
FAQ's
Gift Card Balance
Product, Healthy & Safety Details
Online Web Survey
More Shopping
Retail Store LocatorShop by BrandsDigital CatalogBuy It/Try It - $1.25 & $2.25Online Listing Trending Now
Is Proprietary
Jerry's Artarama has been proudly serving artists since 1968 with only the finest art materials & supplies. We are dedicated to you, the artist! Shop online from a professional art supply store offering quality, selection and the best prices!
2020 JerrysArtarama.com All Right Reserved
Where Artists Shop For The Best Supplies, Values & Service!
Site Map Privacy Policy
About Jerry's Website Features
Contact Us 1-800-U-ARTIST (827-8478)Corporate: 6104 MADDRY OAKS CT. RALEIGH, NC 27616-9997| © 1989-2020 - JerrysArtarama.com
Proudly Serving Artists for Over 50 Years!
Payment Options
Safe & Secure Shopping
